<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://oyra.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://oyra.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-05-24T01:02:03+01:00</updated><id>https://oyra.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Kaya Me</title><subtitle>Welcome to London</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the grumpy London real estate blog</title><link href="https://oyra.github.io/2021/07/26/welcome.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the grumpy London real estate blog" /><published>2021-07-26T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-26T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://oyra.github.io/2021/07/26/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://oyra.github.io/2021/07/26/welcome.html">&lt;p&gt;All the greatness and terribleness of the City of London.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;London is a great city full of amazing people, with all their differences and similarities. And the only thing they have in common is: they live in London, and it’s not made of rubber!
Each of us needs our own piece of private space, and some of that space here is… unusual.
Unusual in a good way, in a curious way or might just… you know, benefit from demolition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latter is what my story is about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for a not so standard apartment in London, or looking at how to get rid of it, please follow along.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I have an imaginary friend, Fred. He just moved to London from another Solar system and is looking for a flat or house to rent. 
As a person who is almost a native Londoner (5 years of residency is quite a lifetime here!) I am trying to help him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some options Fred and I found on popular real estate websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lot number one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/posts_img/2021-07-26__police.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Police car inspired wall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If only our lyrical hero grew up to become a Policeman (or, alternatively, had Tritanopia) he might have been happy (or at least calm) in this kitchen.
An alarming place for the rest of us to be!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;London bedrooms are known to be ridiculously small. Properties are advertised in bedrooms. “2-bedroom apartment” could consist of a kitchen, living room, two double bedrooms and a garden, or it could just be a tiny little kitchen that has been a corridor in Victorian times and two rooms, the only thing that fits in is a bed that has been magically assembled inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a kid I often dreamed of a room where the floor would be soft and I can sleep wherever I want.
Thanks gods (of laughter) today I found my perfect place!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/posts_img/2021-07-26__tiny_bedroom_double_bed.png&quot; alt=&quot;Single bedroom with a double bed&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="London" /><category term="humour" /><summary type="html">All the greatness and terribleness of the City of London.</summary></entry></feed>